[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とまります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "泊ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'れんしゅう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "練習"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せんたく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "洗濯"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そうじ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "掃除"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はじまります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "始まります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんがた' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新型"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひらきます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "開きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "会場"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たのしみます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "楽しみます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おおどおり' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "大通り"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "以上"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぞう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "像"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けいば' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "競馬"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'きょうりゅう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "恐竜"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'たてもの' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "建物"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'うつします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "映します"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'えいぞう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "映像"
    }
]